

55 Sarvis Ridge Road Normandy, Tennessee (TN), United States, 37360 connorwhite812@gmail.com 19315815820

Graduate Computer Science major with focus in cyber security, with several years of work experience as an Operations Manager at a small business. Previously a research assistant at Southern Arkansas University in machine learning methods. Recently gained experience in planning and managing tasks in a web application development team setting under a DoD affiliated company. Looking for opportunities in the software engineering and cyber security industries with potential for advancement and growth.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Intern - Web Application Development

General Infomatics | June 2023 - August 2023

- Aquired DoD security clearance
- 10 week internship duration took place at the Arnold Engineering Development Complex (AEDC)
- Modified existing SQL scripts to account for new and old application version attributes
  - -Necessary for database table creation scripts to work on each project version release
- Applied front end changes in javascript based on user input of prior application versions
- -Grants front end users an active role in visual and functional requirments to promote efficiency
- Developed error checking scripts and test cases to filter out unwanted results
- -Prevents database table creation errors and informs users of problems before they occur
- Gained experience working on real-time applications using commit, rollback, push to origin, and branching practices

#### **Undergraduate Research assistant**

Southern Arkansas University | May 2022 - August 2022

- Familiar with Q-learning, reinforcement learning, and deep reinforcement learning models
- Experience using Python as the primary research language
- Contributed to published research as co-author on reinforcement learning

### **Manager of Operations**

American Mulch | May 2019 - August 2022

- Engaged with existing and potential clients to gain insight into needs
- Directed day-to-day operations by spearheading implementation of short-term and long-term strategies to achieve business plan and profitability goals
- Managed inventory delivery scheduling
- Oversaw training of new heavy machinery operators
- Operated heavy machinery daily (skid loader: bucket and forklift)

## **EDUCATION**

# Master of Science in Computer and Information Sciences

Southern Arkansas University, Magnolia, Arkansas 71753 | August 2019 - May 2024

- 3.83 Cumulative GPA
- Vulnerability and Risk Assessment
- Information and Network Security
- Traceable Systems and Computer Forensics
- Database Management Systems
- Focus in Cybersecurity

# Bachelor of Science in Computer Science with Cyber Security Concentration

Southern Arkansas University, Magnolia, Arkansas 71753 | August 2019 - May 2023

- 3.70 Cumulative GPA
- Capstone project (web development, database integration, vulnerability mitigation, facial recognition, machine learning, HIPAA regulation adherence, and access restriction included within project)
- Software Engineering (CourseWork)
- Pesident's List Honoree
- Computer Science Department Research Assistant
- 5-year Track and Field Scholarship Recipiant
- Decathlon School Record Holder
- Track and Field Team Captain
- Responsible for Track and Fleld related school property over several days during meets

# LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

### **Track and Field Team Captain**

| August 2021 - May 2024

- Led team practices for 3 years (Track and Weightroom)
- Took special interest in mentoring freshman athetes to prevent overexertion injuries, and promote educational requirements to maintain eligibility
- Provided empathetic advise to athletes who could no longer handle the physical stress of athletics by steering them towards a full academic college experience
- Provided council for new and inexperienced recruits by sharing my experiences and giving them clear goals

# **KEY SKILLS**

- Java
- Python
- PHP
- SQL
- Virtual Machines
- Linux
- Network Traffic Monitoring
- API
- JavaScript
- Web Development